(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-15T23:00:57.382892",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
アニメにハマって
I got hooked on anime,
歌いたくなっちゃった！
and now I really want to sing!
推しのシーン見ながら カラオケ歌えるなんて…
Being able to sing karaoke while watching scenes of my fave...
尊すぎてツラいっ！
is so precious, it hurts!
歌いたいアニメ・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Find the anime and game songs you want to sing!
JOYSOUND！
JOYSOUND!
あ、あ、ああ〜
Ah, a, aaa~
本日は、桃鈴ねね 1st Live
Thank you all so much for coming today
『花咲くねねねねねねねね超開花』に
to Momosuzu Nene's 1st Live:
ご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
"Hanasaku Nene Nene Nene Nene Nene Nene Nene Chokaika"!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、
To ensure everyone enjoys the concert until the very end,
いくつかご案内をさせていただきます。
I have a few announcements to make.
お利口だね、みんな。
You're all such good boys and girls.
公演中の撮影、録音、
Photography, audio recording,
録画機材の使用は固くお断りしております。
and the use of video recording equipment during the show are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっておりますので、
Smoking is prohibited inside the venue,
喫煙はご遠慮くださーい。スパスパ禁止でーす。
so please refrain from smoking. No puffing allowed!
そして万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせずに、
Also, in the unlikely event you start feeling unwell, don't push yourself
近くのスタッフへお知らせくださーい。
and please notify a nearby staff member right away.
え、会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、
Furthermore, moshing, diving,
大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、
excessive jumping, throwing items onto the stage,
他の皆の迷惑になったり公演を妨げる行為は、
or any actions that cause trouble for others or disrupt the show
一切禁止としております。
are strictly forbidden.
でも、みんなに飛んでほしいってところもあるから、そこは飛ぼうね。
But there are parts where I want everyone to jump, so let's jump then, okay?
ルールを守って盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's follow the rules and hype things up!
そして、演出の都合上、
Also, due to production requirements,
通路にお荷物を置いたり足を出さないようにしてください。
please do not leave your bags in the aisles or stick your legs out.
これ、とっても重要です。
This is very important.
もしかしたら、荷物とか足が無くなっちゃう恐れがあるので、
Because your belongings or even your legs might disappear otherwise,
ちゃんと収納しておいてくださーい。
so please keep everything neatly stored away!
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、
In addition, video streaming and photo cameras will be operating in the venue,
客席が映り込む場合がございます。
and audience members may be captured on camera.
映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、
Please note that footage and photos may be used for promotional purposes,
あらかじめご了承ください。
so thank you in advance for your understanding.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは「#ねね超開花」です。
Also, the official live hashtag is "#ねね超開花" (#NeneChokaika).
トレンド1位ありがとー！
Thank you for getting it to #1 on trending!
まだまだハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてね。
Keep using the hashtag and keep the hype going!
それでは、開演までもう少しです！
Now then, the concert will begin shortly!
みんなで一緒に盛り上がりましょう！
Let's have an amazing time together!
桃鈴ねねでしたー！
This was Momosuzu Nene!
10！
10!
9！
9!
8！
8!
7！
7!
6！
6!
5！
5!
4！
4!
3！
3!
2！
2!
1！
1!
3、2、1、GO！
3, 2, 1, GO!
桃鈴ねね
[Momosuzu Nene]
桃鈴ねね 1st Live ねねねねねねねね超開花！
[Momosuzu Nene 1st Live: Nenenenenenenene Super Bloom!]
ご注文のスーパーアイドル準備中
16:30に到着予定
[Your ordered Super Idol is being prepared]
[Estimated arrival: 16:30]
準備完了
[Preparation Complete]
配達中
[Out for Delivery]
ああーっ！
Aaaah!
配達中
[Out for Delivery]
東京ガーデンシアター
配達中
[Tokyo Garden Theater]
[Out for Delivery]
ああーっ！
Aaaah!
配達中
[Out for Delivery]
なななな ななじゃなくって
It's not "na-na-na-na, na-na"!
にににに ににじゃなくって
It's not "ni-ni-ni-ni, ni-ni"!
ぬぬぬぬ ぬぬじゃなくって
It's not "nu-nu-nu-nu, nu-nu"!
のののの ののじゃなくって
It's not "no-no-no-no, no-no"!
う〜〜ね！
Ooh... Ne!
ねね！
Nene!
よっしゃよっしゃよっしゃよっしゃ！
Alright, alright, alright, alright!
ねね！
Nene!
よっしゃよっしゃよっしゃいくぞー！
Alright, alright, alright, let's go!
こんねねー！ お手元の桃、桃鈴ねねです！
Kon-nene~! Your very own peach, Momosuzu Nene here!
せーのでカツ丼食べました アイドル志望の大爆走！
On three, I ate a katsudon! The aspiring idol's reckless charge!
朝型ガールで行きましょ ちょっと待機と二度寝で遅刻して
Let's go as morning people, being late from idling and oversleeping!
食欲旺盛 たくさん食べて
Full of appetite, eating plenty,
諦めもわる... サボっちゃうのもしょうがないよねー
Giving up is bad... but slacking off can't be helped, right?
ねねねねねねねね
Nenenenenenene
いぇーい！
Yay!
嫌んなことも あるけど 悔しいことも あるけど
There are unpleasant things, and frustrating things too, but...
大丈夫 ほら前を向いて
It's okay, look ahead!
いつかはきっと スーパーねねち！
Someday for sure, Super Nenechi!
ついてきて ねねねねねねねねね
Follow me! Nenenenenenenene
ねねねねねねねねね
Nenenenenenenene
ねね！
Nene!
ねねねねねねねねね
Nenenenenenenene
ねね！
Nene!
ねねねねねねねね
Nenenenenenene
手振り身振りこそで全開でいこう 思い切りやれば何とかなるよ
Let's go all out with our gestures, do it with all your might and it'll work out!
転んだっていい 落ち込んだっていい 体傾けていこうよね
It's okay to fall, it's okay to feel down, let's lean into it and move forward!
ね ね ね ね ね ね ね
Ne, ne, ne, ne, ne, ne, ne...
大爆走！
Reckless charge!
ねね！
Nene!
よっしゃよっしゃよっしゃよっしゃ！
Alright, alright, alright, alright!
ねね！
Nene!
みんなも一緒に！ よっしゃよっしゃよっしゃよっしゃ！
Everyone join in! Alright, alright, alright, alright!
野菜と果物たくさんと お菓子揃えて準備オッケー
Plenty of veggies and fruits, plus snacks all set—preparation OK!
早起き苦手 掃除も苦手
Bad at waking up early, bad at cleaning too,
やっぱり睡眠て大事だよねー
Sleep really is the most important thing, right?
ねねねねねねねねねねねね
Nenenenenenenenene
たくさんの人に愛されたい
I want to be loved by lots of people!
ちゅっちゅっちゅー！
Chu-chu-chu!
大好きなみんなに愛されたい
I want to be loved by everyone I adore!
ちゅっちゅっちゅー！
Chu-chu-chu!
ここから成るんだ ハイパーねねち！
From here on, I'll become Hyper Nenechi!
やっちゃって！ ねねねねねねねねね
Let's do it! Nenenenenenenene
ねねねねねねねねね
Nenenenenenenene
ねね！
Nene!
ねねねねねねねねね
Nenenenenenenene
ねね！
Nene!
ねねねねねねねね
Nenenenenenene
手振り身振りこそで全開でいこう 歌は誰にも負けたくないな
Let's go all out with our gestures, I don't want to lose to anyone in singing!
大きな声で 走る前に ちょっとトイレに行ってくるねー！
In a loud voice, before running, I'm going to run to the restroom real quick!
もっとみんなが声出してくれないと ねねトイレから帰ってこないかもよー！
If you guys don't cheer louder, Nene might never come back from the restroom!
ねね！
Nene!
せーの！
Ready, set!
なななな ななじゃなくって
It's not "na-na-na-na, na-na"!
にににに ににじゃなくって
It's not "ni-ni-ni-ni, ni-ni"!
ぬぬぬぬ ぬぬじゃなくって
It's not "nu-nu-nu-nu, nu-nu"!
のののの ののじゃなくって
It's not "no-no-no-no, no-no"!
みんなありがとー！ ただいまー！
Thank you everyone! I'm back!
いっくよー！ ねねねねねねねねね
Here we go! Nenenenenenenene
ねねねねねねねねね
Nenenenenenenene
ねね！
Nene!
ねねねねねねねねね
Nenenenenenenene
ねね！
Nene!
ねねねねねねねね
Nenenenenenene
手振り身振りこそで全開でいこう 思い切りやれば何とかなるよ
Let's go all out with our gestures, do it with all your might and it'll work out!
転んだっていい 落ち込んだっていい 体傾けていこうよね
It's okay to fall, it's okay to feel down, let's lean into it and move forward!
ね ね ね ね ね ね ね
Ne, ne, ne, ne, ne, ne, ne...
大爆走！
Reckless charge!
それじゃあ 次の曲へー！
Well then, onto the next song!
ずっと身体に刻まれているんだ
It's been engraved in our bodies all along.
まだまだ夏は終われない！
Our summer isn't over yet!
みんな ラスト曲 盛り上がっていくぞー！
Everyone, let's get hyped for the final song!
ラムネみたいな目で 見上げた放課後
Looking up after school with ramune-colored eyes,
ソーダにもまだ 泡の残ってるかな
I wonder if bubbles still remain in the soda.
ねえ こんな教科書も 嫌なことも
Hey, all these textbooks and unpleasant things,
今だけ忘れさせて 楽しい話をさ
let me forget them for now with fun stories.
じわっと溢れたんだ 胸が教えてくれる
It welled up inside, and my heart tells me so.
僕らは この夏
In this summer, we are...
超開花！
In full super bloom!
ずっと身体に刻まれているんだ
It's been engraved in our bodies all along.
まだまだ夏は終われない
Our summer isn't over yet!
タンタンタン！ 手足でほら パンパンパン！ って鳴らせばさ
Tap-tap-tap! Look, if you clap clap-clap-clap with hands and feet,
バラバラのテンポもいいけど 身体が疼いてもしょうがない
even an erratic tempo is fine; can't help it if your body tingles!
タンタンタン！ 気の済むまで 描いてみたい
Tap-tap-tap! I want to paint until my heart's content!
次も さあ！
Next, come on!
ドキドキ こんな今日もしずかに 乾かしたあの影も
Even the shadow quietly dried on a thrilling day like today,
青いまま 過ぎる前に なんて願ってた
I wished it would stay youthful blue before it slipped away.
飲み切れなかった日々も 炭酸のよい 今なら
Even the days I couldn't swallow whole, with the fizz lingering, now...
これもアクセントって思えた
I can think of them as just an accent.
キラッとさ 見えてた あの頃の僕は
The me from back then, who caught a sparkling glimpse—
少し濁って あの頃のように
even if slightly clouded, just like in those days,
飛び回ったんだ
I soared around!
みんなの青春 今日ここで 今 ねねにいっぱいに見せてください！
Show Nene all of your youth, right here, right now!
大人になればなるほど 僕ら 心が動くことも減るのかな
The more we grow up, I wonder if our hearts are moved less often.
後戻りなんて出来やしないから
Since there's no turning back,
まっすぐ僕のドキドキに
straight toward my fluttering heart!
いつだって躍らされて汗をかいてちゃうような
Constantly dancing to the beat and working up a sweat,
そんな毎日にね ずっとひそかに宝のまんまでいた
in every single day like that, it quietly remained a treasure.
すぐの芽は まだ止まらない
The sprouting buds won't stop growing yet!
タンタンタン！ いくつだってくらい パンパンパン！ 弾けちゃえ
Tap-tap-tap! As many times as you like, clap-clap-clap! Burst right out!
カタカタ 重なる声 モヤモヤも全部飲み干して
Clattering overlapping voices, gulp down all the gloom and haze!
タンタンタン！ 君のまま 描いていて
Tap-tap-tap! Keep painting as your true self!
パッと夜に咲く 一輪の花
A single flower bursting into bloom in the night,
のように 僕ら 確かにここに足跡を残す
just like that, we surely leave our footprints right here.
打ち鳴らせ 満開の
Sound it loud! In full bloom,
あてはまる 言葉が 花束を追い越すの
the fitting words overtake the bouquet!
きっと それくらいでいいの 今更にもう手繰り寄せて
Surely that's just fine; reeling it all in even now,
さあ行こう！
Let's go!
というわけで 始まりましたー！
And with that, it has officially begun!
桃鈴ねね 1st Live『花咲くねねねねねねねね超開花』！
Momosuzu Nene 1st Live, "Hanasaku Nenenenenenene Choukaika"!
じゃあまず ねねの自己紹介をさせていただきたいと思います！
First off, I'd like to do Nene's self-introduction!
ねねが「みんなの心の？」って言ったら みんな何て返すんだっけ？
When Nene says, "Who's in everyone's hearts?", how do you reply?
その通り！ よくできました！
Exactly! Well done!
じゃあいくよー！ ホロライブ・ねぽらぼの「ね」！ みんなの心の？
Here we go! The "Ne" in Hololive's NePoLaBo! Who's in everyone's hearts?
桃鈴ねねでーす！
It's Momosuzu Nene!
もう待ちに待ちに待ちに待った 1st Live！
The 1st Live we've all been waiting and waiting and waiting for!
今回のテーマは「楽しさ最大出力」をテーマに
With this show's theme being "Maximum Joy Output,"
ねねがみんなと一緒に超開花していくっていうライブにしていきたいと思っています！
I want to make this a live show where Nene reaches super bloom together with all of you!
いいねいいね！ 普通のライブと違って みんなが参加してめちゃくちゃ楽しめるようにね
Nice, nice! Unlike a regular live show, so that everyone can join in and have a blast,
いっぱいワクワクとかドキドキを持ってきたから みんな楽しみにしててねー！
I brought lots of excitement and thrills, so please look forward to it!
そして ねねの1stアルバム『Pieceful Story』 みんな聴いてくれた？
And did everyone listen to Nene's 1st album, "Pieceful Story"?
いいね！もうなんかタオルがちょっと汗ばんできてる人がいるくない？
Nice! Aren't there already some people whose towels are getting a bit sweaty?
みんなはどの曲が好きだった？
Which song did everyone like?
せーの！
Ready, go!
おー、おー、おー...
Ooh, ooh, ooh...
ちょっと待って、そ、そっちの人、な、何、何が好き？
Wait a sec, people over there, wh-what did you like?
全部？全部？
All of them? All of them?
こっ、こっちの人は？
Wh-what about the people over here?
全部！全部か！
All of them! All of them, huh!
ねねも全部好きでーす！
Nene loves all of them too!
ありがとう！そして今回は、
Thank you! And this time...
ガールズバンドの生演奏でお届けしていきまーす！
We're bringing it to you with live music from an all-girls band!
ご紹介をさせてくださーい！
Please let me introduce them!
キーボードで、バンドマスターの、しえりーほさん！
On keyboards and Band Master, Shieriho-san!
そして、ギターの、にいづまりおんさん！
And on guitar, Niizuma Rion-san!
かっこいい！
So cool!
そして、ベースの、あいみべーダーさん！
And on bass, Aimi Vader-san!
渋くていいね！
Love that cool vibe!
ドラムの、ばんだななこさんでーす！
On drums, it's Banda Nanako-san!
はい！そしてちょっとね、配信のほうにも触れていきたいと思うんですけど、
Alright! And I'd like to check in with the stream viewers too,
みんなコメントいっぱいありがとーー！
but thank you so much for all the comments!
このへんにね、あの配信の人が見てるカメラがあるの。
Right around here is the camera that the stream viewers are seeing.
いぇーーーい！
Yaaay!
みんなありがと！いっぱいスクショ撮ってねー！
Thank you, everyone! Take lots of screenshots!
そして今回のライブの感想とかはね、
And for your impressions of today's live concert,
全部ハッシュタグ、ももす... あ、違うな、違うな、違うな...
use the hashtag #Momo... ah wait, no, no, no...
ハッシュタグ #ねね超開花 でたくさんポストしてくださーい！
Please post a lot with the hashtag #NeneChouKaika!
そして、今YouTube、そしてTikTokでご覧の方は、次の曲まで聴けるので、
And for those watching on YouTube and TikTok right now, you can listen up until the next song,
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいなーって人は、
so if you want to keep getting hyped up together,
概要欄から配信サイトへGOしてください！
please GO to the streaming site from the description box!
さあみんな！始まる前からギラファねね合唱してたけど、
Alright everyone! You were chanting "Giraffa Nene" even before we started,
まだまだライブ始まってたった2曲だからね！
but the concert's just begun—we've only done two songs!
さっそく次の曲行こうかなー！
Let's get right into the next song!
次は少ししっとりめの曲かな。聴いてください。
The next one is a more mellow song. Please listen.
覚えているかな
Do you remember?
桜色に染まった
It was dyed in the color of cherry blossoms.
帰り道の途中
On the way back home,
流れてく春の吹雪
a spring blizzard of petals drifts by.
隣を歩いて
Walking beside you,
少し背伸びしていた
I tried to stand a little taller.
変わらない距離を
This unchanged distance between us,
本当は縮めたくて
I truly wanted to close.
消えなくて
It wouldn't disappear,
言えなくて
and I couldn't say it.
「またね」じゃ足りないよ
"See you later" isn't enough.
いつかまた会えるかな
I wonder if we'll meet again someday.
君と何回だって 何回だって
No matter how many times, with you,
笑い合えた春の日
on those spring days we laughed together.
風に舞って ふわり消えた
Dancing in the wind, it softly faded away.
それでも忘れない
Even so, I will never forget.
この季節が巡って 離れてく
As this season comes around and drifts away,
言葉を探していた
I was searching for the words.
淡く揺れて 溶けた思い
Feelings faintly swaying and melting away,
それでも忘れない
even so, I will never forget.
「さよなら」じゃなくて
Not a "goodbye,"
ありがとう
but "thank you."
言葉もなくて
Without any words,
胸の奥にしまった
I locked it away deep in my heart.
あどけない気持ち
These innocent feelings,
ホントは伝えたくて
I truly wanted to tell you.
届けたい
I want to reach you,
届かない
but I can't.
「またね」じゃ足りないけど
"See you later" isn't enough, but
いつかまた会えるかな
I wonder if we'll meet again someday.
君と何回だって 何回だって
No matter how many times, with you,
見上げた空の色も
even the color of the sky we gazed up at.
風に乗って ひらり飛んだ花びら
Riding the wind, the fluttering petals flew away.
桃色の
The peach-colored...
これから描く未来地図
The map of the future we're about to draw,
魔法みたいに染めて
is dyed just like magic.
きっとどこにも行かない明日だとしても
Even if tomorrow leads to nowhere...
今も今も褪せない記憶
Even now, memories that never fade,
写真みたいに色づいて
are colored just like a photograph.
ずっとずっと想い出たち 春の色がした
All of those memories had the color of spring.
君と「仲良くだって、仲良くだって」
With you, saying, "We're good friends, we're good friends,"
笑い合えた春の日
on that spring day we laughed together.
風に舞って ふわり消えた
Dancing in the wind, it softly disappeared.
それでも忘れない
Even so, I won't forget.
届きかけた手 ほどかれてく
My reaching hand gently slips away,
言葉を探していた
as I searched for words.
淡く触れて溶けた想い
Feelings that faintly touched and melted away—
それでも忘れない
even so, I won't forget.
さよならじゃなくて ありがとう
Not a "goodbye," but a "thank you."
生まれたてのドキドキを 響かせてみよう
Let's make this brand-new excitement resound!
最高の時間 最高の...
The best time, the best...